scribbleprint.com 2016-03-15

# Privacy Policy < Scribble Print

We value your privacy.

This privacy policy applies to the use of all our web properties including this site.

 **Log Files and Cookies**

This website utilizes industry standard analytics packages which gather limited information on visitors to our website automatically and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage and trends.

Additionally, cookies may be used to provide easier and faster access to website features such as logins and/or repeat visits. Cookies are very small text files that are stored on personal computers for reference purposes. We do not store in cookies to any personally identifiable information in cookies.

 **Links to Third Party Websites**

This website may contain links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by us. Please be aware when you click on any such links; we are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than our own. Consequently, we strongly suggest that you review the privacy policy of every website you visit, whether or not they are linked to by our site.

 **Registration and Use of Personal Information**

Registration is not required in order to use or access this website. However, we may make forums, blogs, message boards or similar features available to our visitors. You may be asked to register for using these features, particularly if you wish to leave comments or publish content.

Please note that if you post comments or articles to any forum, blog or message board on this site, any personally identifiable information you provide in those comments or articles may be read, collated and used by anyone viewing them. As such, we are not responsible for personally identifiable information you may choose to make available through these channels.

 **Security**

We follow accepted industry standards to protect any personal information you have provided to us. However, please be aware that no method of electronic storage can ever be 100% secure. Therefore, as is the case with any organization – we are not in a position to guarantee the absolute security of your information.

You may submit any questions you may have about our security procedures by emailing us

 **Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on our website.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please free to contact us.
